{
    "id": "84356ebc81614ac0a84436cd5a0657cf",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is only putting .............................. an act.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We chatted ........................................ for over an hour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sick .............................. the whole business.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "up",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Put the money ................................., you may need it later.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "by",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The vicar told me I could practice ............................... the organ.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a catch .................................. it somewhere.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge let him ..................................... with a caution.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It came .................................... a lot of money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief was condemned ................................... gaol.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly a bright idea dawned .................................. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}